// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A linear collection of data elements where the linear node is given by means of pointer is called?",
    answer: "linked list",
    options: [
      "linked list",
      "node list",
      "primitive list",
      "None of these"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the time complexity to count the number of elements in the linked list?",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(logn)",
      "None of the mentioned"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of these is an application of linked lists?",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "To implement file systems",
      "For separate chaining in hash-tables",
      "To implement non-binary trees",
      "All of the mentioned"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In circular linked list, insertion of node requires modification of?",
    answer: "Two pointer",
    options: [
      "One pointer",
      "Two pointer",
      "Three pointer",
      "None"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Consider an implementation of unsorted singly linked list. Suppose it has its representation with a head pointer only.Given the representation, which of the following operation can be implemented in O(1) time? i) Insertion at the front of the linked list ii) Insertion at the end of the linked list. iii) Deletion of the front node of the linked list. iv) Deletion of the last node of the linked list ",
    answer: "I and III",
    options: [
      "I and II",
      "I and III",
      "I, II and III",
      "I, II and IV"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What would be the asymptotic time complexity to find an element in the linked list?",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "O(n2)",
      "None of the mentioned"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What kind of linked list is best to answer question like.What is the item at position n?",
    answer: "Array implementation of linked list",
    options: [
      "Singly linked list",
      "Doubly linked list",
      "Circular linked list",
      "Array implementation of linked list"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Linked list is considered as an example of ___________ type of memory allocation.",
    answer: "Dynamic",
    options: [
      "Dynamic",
      "Static",
      "Compile time",
      "None of the mentioned"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following sorting algorithms can be used to sort a random linked list with minimum time complexity?",
    answer: "Merge Sort",
    options: [
      "Insertion Sort",
      "Quick Sort",
      "Heap Sort",
      "Merge Sort"

    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following points is/are true about Linked List data structure when it is compared with array",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "Arrays have better cache locality that can make them better in terms of performance",
      "It is easy to insert and delete elements in Linked List",
      "Random access is not allowed in a typical implementation of Linked Lists",
      "All of the mentioned"

    ]
  },
];